<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Elise Briers</title><link>https://elisebriers.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Elise Briers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://elisebriers.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://elisebriers.github.io/info/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://elisebriers.github.io/info/</guid><description>About Me I&amp;rsquo;m a student at Digital Arts and Entertainment. I&amp;rsquo;m a fluent C++ developer capable of using modern programming patterns to create maintainable and stable applications.
I have a personal interests in modern technologies, hence my preference for modern C++ and Rust. Programming has always been a hobby for me and I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to brining this enthusiasm to the work floor.
Feel free to check out some of my projects or look at my CV.</description></item><item><title>C++ Raytracer</title><link>https://elisebriers.github.io/raytracer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://elisebriers.github.io/raytracer/</guid><description>NOTE: This document describes my learning experience creating this project, see the Github Repo for technical details.
Introduction My raytracer project, made for the Graphics Programming 1 course, is a C++ project that renders 3d figures. It runs completely on the CPU, as GPU ray-tracing was outside of the scope of this course.
Features Rendering of the following objects: Spheres Planes Triangles Triangle meshes (read from an .obj file) A moveable camera positioned in the world The parsing of .</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://elisebriers.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://elisebriers.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Contact me Do you want to get in contact with me? Fill in your information below!</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://elisebriers.github.io/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://elisebriers.github.io/faq/</guid><description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description></item><item><title>Minigin</title><link>https://elisebriers.github.io/minigin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://elisebriers.github.io/minigin/</guid><description> NOTE: This document describes my learning experience creating this project, see the Github Repo for technical details.
Introduction The minigin project was part of the Programming 4 course at Digital Arts and Entertainment. The project is a game engine written in C++, with a qbert clone to show it in action.
Learned Skills During the development of this project, I learned the following skills:
Structuring a large C++ project Usage of programming patterns Parsing Json files Version Control using git</description></item><item><title>Trash Raccoons</title><link>https://elisebriers.github.io/trashraccoons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://elisebriers.github.io/trashraccoons/</guid><description>NOTE: This document describes my learning experience creating this project. Feel free to check out the game itself on Itch.
YouTube Video
Introduction Trash Raccoons is a multiplayer couch coop game created during the Game Projects course at Digital Arts and Entertainment. With a group of 3 people (2 artists and 1 programmer) we where tasked to create a game together.
In Trash Raccoons, players play as raccoons that try to collect as much trash as possible and deliver this trash back to the garbage truck.</description></item></channel></rss>